// Question Types
// 1. MCQs | Multiple Choice | single
// 2. boolean | true/false | single
// 3. MAQs | Multiple Answers | multiple

import { Topic } from '.'

export const Q031: Topic = {
  topic: 'TOEIC Part 5',
  level: 'Beginner',
  totalQuestions: 10,
  totalScore: 10,
  totalTime: 100,
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'Sales representatives at East Greenville Corporation are recommended to ------ utilize their customer database to increase sales.',
      choices: ['actively', 'activity', 'activate', 'active'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['actively'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題301-310/#q301',
    },
    {
      question: 'The conference room fee is included in the standard rate, but an additional fee is charged only ------ you extend the time of use.',
      choices: ['during', 'within', 'consequently', 'when'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['when'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題301-310/#q302',
    },
    {
      question: 'A new tax is being considered for the city’s financial restructuring, but citizens have not responded ------ to the proposal.',
      choices: ['commonly', 'favorably', 'hardly', 'securely'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['favorably'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題301-310/#q303',
    },
    {
      question: 'Ryu Garcia’s latest novel is his ------ book to date and has been translated into several languages.',
      choices: ['popularity', 'most popularly', 'more popular', 'most popular'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['most popular'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題301-310/#q304',
    },
    {
      question: 'As the ------ of East Tera Systems, Mr. Davidson has contributed to creating jobs in the community.',
      choices: ['foundation', 'founding', 'found', 'founder'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['founder'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題301-310/#q305',
    },
    {
      question: 'Due to Ms. Jung’s urgent business trip, tomorrow’s meeting ------ for a later date.',
      choices: ['reschedules', 'will be rescheduled', 'has rescheduled', 'will reschedule'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['will be rescheduled'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題301-310/#q306',
    },
    {
      question: 'After months of ------, Ernest Manufacturing and Herbert Technologies have reached an agreement to merge.',
      choices: ['priorities', 'responsibilities', 'negotiations', 'facilities'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['negotiations'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題301-310/#q307',
    },
    {
      question: 'Tickets for the Seaside Botanical Garden can be purchased ------ at the box office and online.',
      choices: ['not only', 'neither', 'either', 'both'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['both'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題301-310/#q308',
    },
    {
      question: 'If you would like to see a ------ of our new products, just ask one of our staff members at the booth.',
      choices: ['grant', 'mayor', 'profession', 'demonstration'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['demonstration'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題301-310/#q309',
    },
    {
      question: 'The streets ------ North Wood College will be closed from 8 p.m. today until 6 a.m. tomorrow due to construction.',
      choices: ['surround', 'surrounds', 'surrounded', 'surrounding'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['surrounding'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題301-310/#q310',
    },
  ],
}